Alright everybody, just a little bit more and it's finished!Show some spirit!
O-onee-chan! What's this?
Ah Mare, what's up?
I got curious since I heard loud noises. Onee-chan, to call upon a huge pack of dragonkin, What are you making?
Hm-hmm! What do you think?
I wonder...It looks like another Nazarick but...
Exactly! What I'm making is another underground Nazarick! (the entrance way)
Ehh!!
It not just on the outside but the inside is identical too! Well~,amazing right?...Wait, why do you look so frightened?
ï»¿
N-no way...O-onee-chan...
What?
I-it's n-nothing...
Don't try to avoid the topic, give it to me straight!
Ueehawawawawa I-I get it!
Onee-chan, are you planning to declare independence from Nazarick...?
Haaa? Obviously that's not gonna happen.What the heck are you saying?
Ueh~! B-but t-there's no need to make a large base...like this...
Haaa...You...I made this because--
...! This presence!
Gate,Close.
Ainz-sama!
Looks like progress is going smoothly, Aura.
A-ainz-sama!! You came to visit me?
Oh-you've managed to do all this in such a short time. I appreciate it, Aura.
Ehehe~you don't have to thank me~This is Ainz-sama's orders so it's a given!
Eh,then...It was Ainz-sama's order to make another Nazarick?
Indeed. We don't know when an invader will come.
So it is necessary to prepare a dummy Nazarick to lure them in for when that happens.
This just another form of Nazarick defensive countermeasures.
Wow~So that explains it~
Hm? What's the matter?
Ah no, I thought...Onee-chan was planning to go independent.
(Eh? Independent?)
Like I was saying! That's never gonna happen!
UheH! Ouch....Sorry Onee-chan~
Geez! Ainz-sama, please don't misunderstand, okay?
I see.
(Aura's declaring independence? That's not possible! But,there's Shalltear's case too...)
Aaahh *ahem* Aura
What do you want, Ainz-sama?
Is there something you're unsatisfied in your daily life?
Ehh? You mean me?
Yes, you all work your hardest all the time for my sake.
In spite of this, I have given no reward in return. Is there something I can do for you?
W-what are you saying, Ainz-sama. Giving a reward is too much~...
T-that's right! Being able to serve Ainz-sama is a reward in itself!
I'm glad to hear you all say that but, this is something I personally wish for as well.
Ainz-sama's?
Renumerating subordinates for their work is the duty of those in the top and at the same time their happiness.
Now then Aura,is there something you want?
I-it's a little too sudden to ask me this...
You've already accomplished the feat of constructing this dummy Nazarick.There's no need to hold back, you know?
Uh...I really appreciate Ainz-sama's kindness but, I think it's not fair that I'm the only one receiving a reward.
Is that so?
The other Guardians are also working hard for Ainz-sama's sake as well. Being the only one to receive a reward feels really weird.
T-that's true...if only Onee-chan gets a reward and Albedo-san and Shalltear-san finds out...!
(Right...It's gonna be troublesome.)
I understand. We will discuss this at the next meeting.
I think that's a very good idea, Ainz-sama!
Well then, farewell.
Ahhh...Aura,...
I-is something the matter?
Looking forward to working with you.
!!..Yes!
--that is all for the agenda for today, any questions?
There is one last thing I'd like to talk about if you don't mind, Albedo.
Ainz-sama, of course. Please discuss it with us.
First of all, I would like to thank you all for coming today. I am very grateful to all your daily work.
Ainz-sama! Your words are wasted on us. However, we are all working all for the sake of--
Albedo! I'm still in the middle of talking.
!!My deepest apologies.
Kefufufufu~ Looks like your point-earning has failed~
Oh my Shalltear, Whatever do you mean by that?
All your buttering up is having the reverse effect.
Buttering up!? All I want is to confess my honest feelings as Ainz-sama's faithful servant!
A faithful servant, you say?
--is a faithful servant supposed to have a hug pillow of her master and drools all over it?
Shalltear, embarrassing me in front of the Supreme One, You'd better be prepared.
Ara ara~there are wrinkles forming on your face~isn't that a big problem for a succubus?
Let's settle this outside!!
Enough.of this.already! We are.before the.Supreme One.
Hh! My deepest apologies!
I'm terribly sorry!
What.a shameless.bunch.
This happens all the time, it's about time you learn from it.
If you may, Ainz-sama, Please continue the rest.
Actually to repay everyone's work, I am planning to introduce a welfare system to Nazarick.
Wel-fare system? What is that?
The world that I was previously living in had something called a 'company'
Well, you could think of it as something like a guild.
It would take a long time if I were to explain it in detail...
Basically it is the name of the system a company offers to their members, to help them work comfortably.
(In reality there are many companies that don't maintain it though. I have never　benefited from it after all.)
A service, huh...
Exactly. For a start, I am thinking of building　new facilities that you wish for inside Nazarick.
Making Nazarick more comfortable would contribute to the reinforcement of Nazarick after all.
Do you have any wishes?
Ainz-sama... I think it is a great proposal, but Nazarick already has enough variety of facilities in my opinion.
9th floor even has a Spa Resort and a Bar after all.
There is even a Nail Saloon. Thanks to that I can preserve my beautiful nails.
From.a.Snowy.Mountain, to.a.Jungle. I.Think.it.Would.be.Harder.to Find.Something.We.Don't.Have.
Hmmm, I see...
Umm...
Oh, it's rare to see Mare speak!
Recently, after talking with Ainz-sama I was thinking about it...
No need to be reserved, Nazarick is your　place too.
Any kind of wish will be made real.
Then.. I want to request an ocean!
An ocean, is it?
Yes! I was thinking if we had an ocean near the jungle in the 6th floor, we could raise many more animals and plants!
You... There　is something called a limit in everything!
Was that no　good, after all?
Well, for now I am just hearing your opinions.
Hmmm... If I were to say it, maybe a torture room?
We.Already.Have.a.Torture.Room in.the.5th.Floor don't.We?
You see, I want more variation. Fire torturing, water torturing,　ishidaki (rock cradling), medication and　maybe Sai no Kawara (Torture of Dead Men) could be good too.
I-I see...
What about you onee-chan?
Me? I guess maybe an animal training facility that I can swing my whip　with all my strength.
How.is.That.Any.Different From.a.Torture.Room?
Training and torture is entirely different! You can't call it training, if you don't put love in it!
You can't call it torture either if you don't do it with love, Aura.
Is that so?
Ainz-sama! May I humbly ask for something?
Y-Yeah. I don't mind.
If it can be done, could we have a children's room?
Haah?
It would have pink walls, a hanging toy from the ceiling and a baby bed at the center.
Why would you need such a thing?
It doesn't concern you does it?
Well if you want to make one, you can do it, but I will be partaking in the design.
The walls black, the hanging toy will be a bat and the baby bed will be changed into a cradle.
Why are you intervening!?
Of course, I will be first one who will be using that room after all.
It seems like we need to settle this fight, Shalltear.
Oh, why do we need to carry out a fight that we know the result of?
Yes you are right, of course I will be the one who bears the child of the Supreme Being even if we don't...
Ainz-sama, lets talk about the decoration of the room!
GET AWAY FROM AINZ-SAMA YOU BITCH!
BE QUIET!!
I am very sorry!
Forgive my insolence!
Isn't this a Déjà vu?
Sigh... This topic will be carried over to the next discussion. Dismissed!
Ainz-sama, where are you going?
Its a personal business.